myprovisionstore.com 2018-01-17

# Grocery Shopping Online - Buy fruits, vegetables & other household essentials at MyProvisionStore online grocery store & get Free home delivery!

Your privacy is important to 'MyProvisionStore.com' We want to make you feel comfortable and secure shopping in our store. This privacy policy explains the types of information we gather, how it is protected, what we do with it and how you can correct or change information. By shopping at MyProvisionStore.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. Your use of MyProvisionStore.com means that you accept the practices described in this Privacy and Security Policy as changed from time to time.

You can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, As part of the registration process on the MyProvisionStore, MyProvisionStore collect the following personally identifiable information about you: Name including first and last name, alternate email address, mobile phone number and contact details, Postal code, Demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address etc.) and information about the pages on the site you visit/access, the links you click on the site, the number of times you access the page and any such browsing information. You select a email/username and password allowing you access to the MyProvisionStore Service.

MyProvisionStore also receives and stores certain types of information whenever you interact with us through the use of "cookies." Cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide you with certain shopping features. These "cookies" allow us to give you customized and personalized service and helps us identify ways to improve your shopping experience. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to reject or disable cookies or receive notice when a new cookie appears. If you choose to reject or disable cookies, you will be unable to use those MyProvisionStore Services that require the use of such cookies. MyProvisionStore.com's cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information. 

If you choose to buy on the Website, we collect information about your buying behaviour. 

If you transact with us, we do not collect information, such as a credit/debit card number and a credit/debit card expiration date. 

If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, credit card / debit card / other payment instrument details, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with us. While you can browse some sections of our Website without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests.

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control, MyProvisionStore has in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, MyProvisionStore servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and your information is shared with employees and authorised personnel on a need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you. Although MyProvisionStore will endeavour to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that MyProvisionStore will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

To correct or update any information you have provided, the Site allows you to do it online. In the event of loss of access details you can send an e-mail to: info@myprovisionstore.com

MyProvisionStore reserves the right to change or update this policy at any time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to the Site.
